jonnyelwyn.co.uk 2019-05-01

# Contact Jonny Elwyn | Jonny Elwyn - Film Editor

Jonny Elwyn is a freelance film editor and writer, living and working in London, UK.

As a freelance film editor he works for a diverse range of clients, handling everything from on-set rushes and offline editorial through to the final sound mix and colour grade.

As a freelance writer he has written for sites like [PremiumBeat.com](http://www.premiumbeat.com/blog/author/jonnyelwyn/ "Jonny Elwyn on Premium Beat.com"), [Rocketstock.com](https://www.rocketstock.com/blog/author/jonny-elwyn/), [Frame.io](https://blog.frame.io/?s=elwyn) and [RedsharkNews](http://www.redsharknews.com/post/itemlist/user/13522-jonny-elwyn "Jonny Elwyn on Redshark News") among others.

He is also the author of [_How To Be A Freelance Creative_](https://jonnyelwyn.co.uk/how-to-be-a-successful-freelance-creative/ "How To Be A Freelance Creative"), a deeply practical guide to building a successful freelance career.

To get in touch with any questions, comments or suggestions, or if you’re interested in learning more about sponsorship opportunities, just fill in your details….

**Affiliate Links**

Jonnyelwyn.co.uk makes use of various affiliate programs which help to support the enormous amount of time needed to research, create and regularly update, the hundreds of posts on this site.

No editorial decisions are ever swayed by the use of affiliate links and it never adds to the cost of a product or service. In some circumstances the affiliate link [actually provides a discount](https://jonnyelwyn.co.uk/film-editing-freebies-promo-codes/).

If you have any questions, just drop them in the box above, I’d be happy to answer them as best I can. Otherwise, thank you for supporting the blog, I hope you’ve found it useful!

As an Amazon Associate I earn from qualifying purchases.

**Sponsored Content**

I get asked all the time to write about specific brands and products. Very occasionally, I agree to do so if I think the product would be of genuine interest to myself or my readers.

In these instances I ask the company to cover the cost of the time it takes to research, write and update the content. This is what a sponsored post means on my blog.

I retain complete editorial control, I write what I like and I say what I want. That’s the deal.

To provide some context, there are well over 700 posts on this site (and counting) and so far four of them have been sponsored.

If you have any questions, do drop me a note in the form above.

**Privacy Policy**

This is mostly cribbed from WordPress’ suggested privacy policy statement. Hopefully it will suffice!

_Who I am_

Jonny Elwyn is a freelance film editor and writer. My website address is: https://jonnyelwyn.co.uk.

_What personal data we collect and why we collect it_

If you make a comment or sign up to the weekly newsletter then you need to input your name and email address for those to function. I also run Google Analytics and Jetpack Stats to keep track of aggregate visitors, page views etc.

_Comments_

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymised string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it.

The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/

After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

_Contact forms_

If you use the contact form to get in touch with me then your name ad email only comes through to me and I don’t retain these for any other purpose than our on-going conversation.

_Cookies_

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies.

These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies.

This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices.

Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year.

If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

_Embedded content from other websites_

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.).

Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

_Analytics_

I run Google Analytics and WordPress Jetpack.

_Who we share your data with_

No one.

_How long we retain your data_

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognise and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile.

All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

_What rights you have over your data_

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us.

You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

_Where we send your data_

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

_Contact information_

Contact me through the contact form above or on my social media handles if you have any further questions about all of this.
